time, friends, I have
brought something for you guys which will be
very strong for me and can
give very good returns in the coming time, so let's take a look at
which are those of the city, their
Twitter problem and requested Udayveer
Void completely agree with u,
this is already what I have brought for you guys,
ONGC, ONGC means boys, school,
girls doing
[music]
all set to grow, it looks very good
consolidation solid in this, that this is the one above, so
in 5 years, in the coming week you
can
subscribe and
subscribe and that this is how
they will go, you school, multibarrel,
why
subscribe
Waghmare, so at this time, I
mean, it is
skinned, that is, the
longer you do it,
I don't think that
it can reach only 40 again and
I will talk more than that,
I will come, so like and
comment, so subscribe, how to
lock the Uday, stoploss is 160, if you
want, you can support long term will by putting a stoploss of 150, I feel it will reach
192 in the attempt
According to fault 150 and if we talk about the second item then
stoploss of 150 in guys keep in mind up to 150,
apart from that I 13
other contestants who
want to keep long term, either above 12320,
scientific team should also update and share
and if the call comes then you
can like it near 155, eighth both of them which will give very
good investment level, you must have
understood, I can see its request micro
fraction or one year target as well,
more than 120, 170 share 260
is seen giving a return of ₹100 and I should also
tell you that only the placement of the chart is
technical tension, if I click on it then
this deal is giving,
if I talk like that then its targets are
coming out, they also
appear creative to me at the moment and
in opposition I am giving you alarms in the public domain, so
I too and suicide due to
declining, this is coming
Why am I saying this, I want to tell you something about them, a
little about Anil,
Shatrughan, please
subscribe, do
the
subscribe,
because of that, it has already
started increasing
and many more, these brothers will not go to the office
and the profitability will increase further,
even after Govind Sharma, I am talking about studying till the brain, according to
that, you are not launching these
companies, net profit making and secondly, the promoter
holding of his, 121 promoters, I mean, I
will definitely comment that even if I am removed, then there
is an FIR in Brilliant Student S8, 70%
stake in it is of foreign investors, who have
sold goods worth more than Rs 1.40 lakh crore, Rs 1.30 lakh crore
in the last two months, despite that
they have a good holding in it and subscribe to them
and
it
happens
that the
normal rate is all very
serious number 1091 rupees and if you
boil it and do drama,
in my opinion, what I am going to lose will be that
I will buy it and Kavita will
go to 218 or even more  Until it
achieves my targets, and if it's
around the holidays, I'll
book my sights on the market around that time,
and after that, I'll ride the rest of the negative auditions. If
you want, you
can adopt this saree and do it. In this way, this will come
into my life,
and I won't be at fault, and I'll commit suicide.
And why should I say that it will increase in the future?
Some people also believe
that if electronic devices come tomorrow, then
corruption and fakirs will be cut. Hello viewers,
Vitamin E capsules will be cut. Otherwise, let me tell you
that yes, convention after convention will increase, because the
Ganga crematorium will increase. At the same time,
March will increase a lot. It will
not be completely ready. The reason is that even now, the
electronic changes that I'm making, the machinery that is being
made, cannot replace the worn engines. The
trailers, the big containers that are
opened for schools, but you go to schools, the
big ones and the loot swell,
we can't replace them right now. Laptops.
Our technology is also present in this note
Australia tour level where they can
replace pet competition
and this will remain if and anyway I will
come after shooting and if you think in the temple
that why are our tensions military
utensil comes then do you think
that the request will not be able to cover it and it is
needed for heavy machinery do
not bend
that Indian oil is in danger no and so I will
dance sandals sisters there are other products so that
Ghagra is going to
increase
and more than convention I still feel that
this is a
low end thing in which the number of subscribers is going to
increase more friend one who is reading seriously
and because of that
very few have been kept which are going to increase
ghr ghr ghr ghr it will
not be a big deal
that the target spoon refine is
1018 so for a cotton which is within 10 days
I think it will be
visible soon and after that it can reach 90
so in this mask I
told you that you can do it friends and let's
see that
ghr
ICICI
General  The insurance company is
ensuring this and if you buy it and
my account is
made with the school, then you can do it, if you want to get rid of it, then
you can do it whose house and if
you commit suicide, then the
reason is that only after that it will be 1000 2253,
it is visible and after that
Jhaal Digest Metro Time, it is
easily going up to 1314 hundred fifteen hundred, the people who will give you the
drink will reach 1550 in between six months to one
year and even more than that, as it is
believed on many channels that in the coming
important six months to one year,
I also believe that Nifty was a
complete trading rowdy, the number of
glasses had broken, according to me,
I have
subscribed to the channel, if you do it, then
in 2002, you will invest very fast
and for
that, if you
want to
think about it, then
here in Dars On Global Academy, I too am a
spoonful of sugar, Deepak who is Prem and he is
also very simple and because of that, I feel that
now the loss to India will be less and
in disgusting works  It has become involved, it is
visible in the urine that oil is being produced, but in reality, the
deposit account receiver is giving
that last display and it is saying that there is a
discount too, which
means that by increasing the percentage to 50 percent, it will
not be a big deal, it means
that this Chakli is going to come to us as a fuel
crude, it will
benefit even more, but it will give, let's
talk first, so let's
look at you know ICC Chief Insurance,
friends, there are many reasons in this, that is why
I am seeing it increasing, and first of all,
as I
tell them, there are retirement benefits in the first sweater,
life bomb technicals,
completely, then 1342 is seen coming,
in this, if you make 1269 100 on the purchase of 1270,
then it is visible in positive territory at
Kochi Yadav in TV and after that,
even till 2050, I do not see it very far,
and after that, I am calling it multi-year,
why am I saying this because friends,
on its beam  Share 6.47 that when very good closed
many good pak shares are made and now
in the coming time more these are going to start
that
they request you all to fix
that now you will get the idea good for insurance
industry and as being in
endurance company I am sure that I know it very
well
chief
a proof find multibagger in this chapter the
objective is a bank story if I do
n't tell you then please search on Google
how much it was making in 2008
and after that for how many years
even after being made fit and how much it is sitting and still
how much is left for it then do new sexy
story HDFC Bank ICICI Bank this
means that these are some lions who can never lose
if you keep them as drama but in
such a situation the building of promoters is very good at
this point send father day in that
chairman theirs is fine
subscribe to this hen
subscribe to the channel that every rest of the public has
very nice day school at point 5 send and
share with details and withdraw them but
if you use  You can
subscribe
and subscribe very quickly, the
next two are very good
for trading as well, there is a very small stop loss at the
end and if you want, you can
use them for trading, you can
use them for mountain
shifting the master plan, the fundamentals of the skin are
also strong and the technique is
recharge system and what I am giving in this,
if you pay attention to these, you will
give a very good return, so next year
this Kotak Bank, Kotak Bank, the current trend is
more than 100 and in this, if you
keep a roti notice stop loss, if the date
closes below this level, then you can
consolidate it on the next day, which I do
not think will happen now, so Dave, no
market has started moving and the Benz is already
separated, they have not yet given the majority, the
corrections that have happened,
so
if you go and
subscribe, there is
nothing in 1806, you can understand
and subscribe, it
seems to have happened for 18000 versus 706,
so the bank has a lot to do  As soon as I
started doing something in the bank, then I
and Navdeep posted bank study
214 movement
a lesson, if you want then you can make good money by saving this past
and let's see the
next stock, the next Industries you are
interested in price is 80, then
you can buy it by putting a small stop loss of 11%,
disclosing Giloy roti and Nagar, it happens
any day, then you can buy it the next day
or else it is
900 to 1000 in the list,
now let me tell you further
why I have kept these two cities
here, not only because they are
visible on the technical charts and I am
giving a small stop loss in Mainpur,
that is the reason, but their fundamentals are
very strong, their profits have
grown by almost 30% in most of the teams,
not only have they doubled, their
properties have doubled, the margins are good
and their fundamentals are very strong,
excise and festivals are
in form for subscription
and Aarti industry is also very good
Heroine is its, if you open its chart and see,
you will come to know that if you
see its monthly chart, it never
falls down, it is continuously going up, there is a
little retracement, after that it goes up again,
but it does something different, it
gives a little interest and then goes ahead, so
if you want, you
can also fold these as multi-bags, as
I always say, you
buy these, when a small profit starts
coming in it, then book your parcel profit,
small but capital gets reduced, some capital comes
back home, then it
gives a bigger profit, then book more parcels and
after that when you make a profit up to 16-17 percent,
20% in which your total capital will come out, then
after that you can fold these
for a long ride and respect to give, it is the
time of wonderful retention, the
rest of the friends, it is good, only keep connected to connected
and also included the
profitable
thread, that chapter note,
second
aspect
and I give
and  If you want, you can see the old record, you
can check it by going to mine, it will be very good
and
keep playing, remember me in your prayers, stay happy,
see you in the next video, thank you so much.